<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Marriage Point Calculator</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help">HELP</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">ABOUT</string>
    <string name="help_text"><b>Finding Route</b>\n\n
        1. Click on <b>Find Route</b>\n
        2.Enter Source and Destination.
        The possible stops will be displayed when three characters are entered in each input section.
        3.Click Search Route.\n\n
        Path 1:\n
        Shortest path between the source and destination will be displayed base on public vehicle routes available.\n
        The path information will include travel transits with available routes, distance and transport fare for each transit and total distance and total fare of transit.\n
        Path2:\n
        A single route between source and destination will be displayed if available.\n
        Each path cah be seperately viewed in map to visualize the path information.
        4. Click on [VIEW DEATAIL] to view more details about route. It will display details regarding routes like intermediate stop map view.


 \n\n<b>Nearby Location</b>\n
        An alternative is provided to user where the user can select source from (at max. four) nearest stops based on aerial distance between the current location of user and nearby stops.
 \n\n<b>Viewing Route Details</b>\n
        1. Click on <b>View Route</b>\n
        2. Click on a route from the list\n
        3. The details of route will be shown in map and each stop name can be viewed by clicking on stop icon.\n
        <b>Detail Route</b>\n
        Detail Route will contain two section.
        \na. Transit:\n
        This section will contain detail regarding route. It will show intermediate transit stops and available routes for given transit
        \nb. Map:\n
        This section will show display all the transit position in an offline map where user can visualize the route. User can also tap on stop icon to see the stop name.
</string>

    <string name="disclaimer_text">
        Travel Fare shown in this app is calculated according to the fare rates provided by DOTM. Local fares may vary.
        Fares shown in the app should be taken as only reference. Developers do not guarantee the correctness of fare displayed.
</string>

    <string name="about_text">
        The “KTM Public Route” is the app which aims to provide the offline route for the users who needs to navigate new places.
        The main purpose of this app is to provide the overall comfort for any user to browse the different routes along with the transport fares needed for the ride.
       It has been developed as Final Year Project in Nepal Engineering College by <b>Sudin Gurung, Sushant Suwal</b> and <b>Som Prasad Shrestha</b> under Supervision of Assistant Professor and  <b>Dinesh Dangol</b> and Department of Computer Science and Engineering.\n

       Features:\n
       1. Source and destination can be chosen from the places stored in the database.
        Shortest path based on the location provided will be displayed.\n
       2. A single route will be displayed if there exists between source and destination.\n
       3. Series of routes with start and end points (with the distance between the points) will be displayed that will take the user from the given source to the required destination.\n
       4. The source can be taken as current location based on GPS and destination will be chosen from the databased stored place.
        The shortest path between location and the destination will be shown.\n
       5. Nearest places will be calculated as aerial distance between current location and all possible location from database.
        Four nearest stops will be taken into account while calculating\n
        6. Concept of Walking distance has been implemented where user can set the maximum preferred walking distance. If any transit route has distance less than the preferred distance than app recommmends to walk instead of taking any public route.\n
       7. The travel cost (for all the transit including travel distance in every transit will be displayed) based on the fare details provided by the Department of Transport Management.\n
        8. The routes will also be shown in the map for better understanding of route.\n
        9. Updates notification will be displayed if any update is released from server.\n\n\n
        Disclaimer:\n
        यो एप्लिकतिओनमा देखायिएको भाडादर यातायात ब्यबस्था बिभागले प्रकाशित गरेको भाडादर अनुसार हो।
        Travel Fare shown in this app is calculated according to the fare rates provided by DOTM. Local fares may vary.
        Fares shown in the app should be taken as only reference. Developers do not guarantee the correctness of fare displayed.\n\n
       If you find any bug in App, Please report it email addresses\n
        ktmpublicroute@gmail.com

</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test_main">TestMainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_auto_complete">KTM Public Route</string>
    <string name="title_activity_async_main">AsyncMainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="title_activity_device_list">DeviceListActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="non_paired">No paired Device</string>
    <string name="title_activity_arduino_main">ArduinoMain</string>
    <string name="title_activity_route_detail">RouteDetailActivity</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Detail</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Map View</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Section 3</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tabbed_main">TabbedMainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail">DetailActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_details">Details</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_welcome_tabbed">WelcomeTabbed</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
